[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these American zoos does NOT house Komodo Dragons?", "correct_answer": "Bronx Zoo", "incorrect_answers": ["Honolulu Zoo", "Disneys Animal Kingdom", "Memphis Zoo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which film did Penelope Cruz and Tom Cruise star together?", "correct_answer": "Vanilla Sky", "incorrect_answers": ["Collateral", "Open Your Eyes", "The Girl of Your Dreams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Shmoo, referenced by the Boss in the film Lucky Number Slevin, was actually a cartoon character in the late 70s.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the full Greek name of the Delta house in the comedy Animal House?", "correct_answer": "Delta Tau Chi", "incorrect_answers": ["Delta Phi Epsilon", "Delta Rho Omega", "Delta Gamma Rho"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Joaquin Phoenix, who portrays singer Johnny Cash, does all his own singing in the film.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the actor who plays Kirbys boss at St. Elmos bar in the movie St. Elmos Fire?", "correct_answer": "Blake Clark", "incorrect_answers": ["Brian Doyle-Murray", "Brian Dennehy", "Charles Durning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take Saturn to complete one orbit around the Sun?", "correct_answer": "just under 30 years", "incorrect_answers": ["just over 20 years", "18 years exactly", "about 15 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The atmosphere of Mars is mostly composed of what element?", "correct_answer": "Carbon Dioxide", "incorrect_answers": ["Methane", "Oxygen", "Hydrogen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many million of earthworms were exported from Canada and sold worldwide in 1980?", "correct_answer": "370 million", "incorrect_answers": ["225 million", "260 million", "100 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brian Hayes coined the term umop-episdn.  What does it mean?", "correct_answer": "Topsy-turvy", "incorrect_answers": ["A computer glitch", "Alien language", "A mishmash of languages"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the abbreviations on prescriptions called?", "correct_answer": "sig codes", "incorrect_answers": ["sib abbreviations", "sif abbreviations", "sic codes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is part of the frontal lobe, an area at the front of each cerebral hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "precental gyrus", "incorrect_answers": ["fusiform gyrus", "cingulate sulcus", "cingulate gyrus"]}]